integration, different school lives. A.
Toby is an exchange student from the USA and is studying at Sunshine Middle School now.
He is comparing his school in the USA with Sunshine Middle School.
Read what he wrote and answer the questions below.
My school back home in the USA is quite different from Sunshine Middle School.
Our classes are not as big as the ones here and we have fewer students in each class.
Here students stay in their own classroom for most of their lessons.
However, in the USA we usually go to different classrooms to have different lessons.
Students here do not change classrooms as often as we do, so they spend more time with their classmates and get to know each other better but we get to know more students.
Students here have students books for most of their subjects but we only have textbooks for a few subjects.
We often need to borrow books from the library or search online to finish our homework.